Guide to the Parents, Families and Friends of Lesbians and Gays (PFLAG) records, 1972-2009.
Parents, Families and Friends of Lesbians and Gays (PFLAG) records
- Series I. Administration
  - Chapter Information
    - Chapter Welcome Kit, 1991-1992 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      a.k.a. "Packet B," sent when a new chapter is established - Parts I and II
    - Membership, 1985-1986 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Membership, 1986-1987 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Chapter Survey, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Misc. chapter newsletters, 1989-1990, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - General materials, 1989-1991 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Background resources, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Chapter Planning, 4/1991 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Chapter Development Manual drafts, 1991-1992 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Chapter Newsletters, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Chapter Development, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Chapter size lists, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Chapter Development guide memo, 199? (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - General chapter materials, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Chapter Summary, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - International, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - National awards program, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Chapter Management, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Chapter Membership Certificate, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - State information, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Chapter Start-up informational packet draft, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Chapter Awards Program, 1992-1993 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Chapter Awards, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Chapter Awards Nomination Materials, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Membership, 1985-1986 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Chapter organization guide, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Lobbying rules for chapters, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Chapter start-up kit, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Chapter leaders, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Strategic chapter planning, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Chapter suggestions, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - How-to handbook for chapters and representatives, 1996 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Chapter awards, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Affiliate awards, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Chapter spotlight, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Misc. chapter materials, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Various chapter start-up documents, 1998-1999 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Chapter directory, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 4-5)
    - "Lobbying Rules & Limitations for P-FLAG Chapters", 1993 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Chapter Manual, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Lake Charles, LA chapter, 1991-92 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Chapter survey, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Chapter to Rep transition, 1999 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Chapters/Reps deleted, 1999 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Ashville, NC sexual abuse allegations, 1999 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Tampa chapter, 1999 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - San Diego chapter, 2000 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Arkansas chapter conflicts, 2000 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Arkansas Chapters: Carolyn Wagner, 2000 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Arkansas Chapter controversy, 2000 (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Fayetteville controversy, 2000 (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Toledo chapter: John Hemstreet resignation, 2000 (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - New chapters, 2000-2002 (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - Chapter startup, 2000-2003 (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - Chapter outreach, 2002-2003 (Box 52, Folder 20)
    - Denver chapter fundraising difficulties, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 21)
    - Clackamas county chapter, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 22)
    - North Iowa chapter, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 23)
    - Key West chapter, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 24)
    - Lower Columbia, WA chapter, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 25)
    - Chapter Publications (Midwestern States), 1993-2009 (Box 65, Folder 36)
      PFLAG Information Brochures: Austin, TX; Columbus, OH; Dayton, OH; East Texas; Kansas City, MO; Lima, OH; Youngstown.
    - Chapter Publications (Midwestern States), 1993-2009 (Box 65, Folder 37)
      "Searching for Common Ground" forum, Columbus OH; "Athens Area P-FLAG Update;" "Sandra Pailet Memorial Scholarship Champagne Reception," New Orleans, LA;" "Opening of Eddie and Velma Dwyer Community Center," Waco, TX; "A Fundraiser at Lincoln's 'Q,'" South Central NE; "Professional Issues in Working with Gays, Lesbians, and Their Families," Fargo, ND; "Ignite-SA: San Antonio's Own GLBT Magazine"
    - Chapter Publications (Midwestern States), 1993-2009 (Box 65, Folder 58)
      "PFLAG Cleveland: State of the Chapter;" "PFLAG Cleveland Someone you know and love is gay" brochure; "People Don't Get Fired for Being Straight;" "Cleveland International Film Festival March 6-16, 2008;" "Cleveland 2007-2008 LGBT Vistors Guide;" "Human Rights Campaign dinner and auction"
  - Computer Services, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Computer Results Unlimited/Thom Unger
  - Consultants, 11/1990 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Ann Thompson Cook, INSITE
  - Dealers, 1989, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    The Book Service, Different Drummers
  - Development, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Affiliate (Chapter) Development Committee
  - Development, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Centers for the Handicapped, Charitable Choices, Inc., Oram Group, Trans-National Financial Services
  - Development, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Director search, administration
  - Development, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Director search, applications
  - Development, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Eichler Reception, thank-you's
  - Dues, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Correspondence and faxes re dues
  - Executive Director Search, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Applications, resumes
  - Finances and Fundraising
    - Audit authorization, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Bequests/Memorials: Benov, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Bequests/Memorials: Cohen, Feltman, Gland, Langguth, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Bequests, General; Memorials, Miscellaneous, 1989-1991 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Board Expense Project notes, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Budget: proposals, reports, calculations, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 40-41)
    - Budget: proposals, reports, calculations, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Budget Workshop, 1990-1993 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Credit Applications: Adams National Bank; automated graphic imaging/copy center; CAI Printing Inc.; Catterton Company, Inc.; NFL Films Video; Quality Motel, Silver Spring, 1990-1994 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Deposits:Copies of checks, calculations, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Invoices, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Promissory notes, royalties, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Statements, 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Stocks: A. G. Edwards, Sperry and Associates, Kemper Securities, power to sell stocks, statements, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - IRS documents, 1982, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Budget figures, 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - IRS: Forms, copies of checks, correspondence, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Banks: Adams National Bank, Citibank TDA, Colorado National Bank, Mutual of America, Nations Bank, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Development Packet, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - District incorporation papers, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Finance Committee, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Finances: Historical, 1991-1993 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Tax information, 1988-1990 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Foundations: Grant information, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - 990 forms, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Schedule A to 990, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - 990 forms, 199 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Financial statement, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Accounting codes, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Budget, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Financial statements, 1990-1991 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Budgeting info., 1992 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Balance sheet, 7/1994 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Accounting, 1994-1995 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Budget, 8/1995 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Budget, 1995-1996 (Box 23, Folder 19-20)
    - March on Washington surplus funds proposal, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Fundraising: direct mail samples, 11/1988 (Box 25, Folder 32-33)
    - Fundraising: direct mail appeal, 10/1988 (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Fundraising: direct mail samples, 2/1989 (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - Fundraising: direct mail samples, 3/1989 (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - Fundraising: direct mail samples, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - Fundraiser, 10/2/1991 (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - Akron chapter donation to National P-FLAG, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 39)
    - Fundraising: direct mail information, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - Fundraising: direct mail samples, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 41)
    - Fundraising information packet, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 42)
    - Corporate funding, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 43)
    - Fundraising: Foundation Center leads, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 44)
    - Miller Brewing Co., 1993 (Box 25, Folder 45)
    - Fundraising: Greve, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 46)
    - Fundraising: Chicago resource center, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 47)
    - Sample fundraising/donation letters, 19893 (Box 25, Folder 48)
    - Planned giving project, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 49)
    - Grant writing, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 50)
    - Grant/support proposals, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 51)
    - Grant/proposal materials and ideas, 1993-1995 (Box 25, Folder 52)
    - Grant/proposal materials and ideas, 1994-1995 (Box 25, Folder 53)
    - Pride grant notes, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 54)
    - Individual donor leads, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 55)
    - Funding meetings, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Donor/advertising files, 1994-1995 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Philip Morris Co., 1995 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Donor/finance file, 1995? (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Fundraising: foundations/corporations, 1993-1995 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Resources- leads, advice, $, assistance, 1994-1995 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Reaching Out: A Grantmakers' Guide to Lesbian and Gay Issues, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Direct Mail, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Triplex Direct Mail return counts, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - PFLAG Balance Sheet, 7/31/94 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - PFLAG Funding Guide, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Tax Exempt # (IRS), 1994 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Federation Benefits and Salary Analysis, 1991-93 (Box 52, Folder 26)
    - Accounting, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 27)
    - IRS, 1994-2002 (Box 52, Folder 28)
    - Expense reporting and regional budgets, 1998-99 (Box 52, Folder 29)
    - Finances, 1998-99 (Box 52, Folder 30)
    - Chapter dues, 1999 (Box 52, Folder 31)
    - Delinquent dues, 1999 (Box 52, Folder 32)
    - Chapter Dues collection, 1999 (Box 52, Folder 33)
    - Board fundraising, 1995-98 (Box 52, Folder 34)
    - Financial reporting/501(c)(3) resources, 1999 (Box 52, Folder 35)
    - Financial statements, Sept. 30, 2000 (Box 52, Folder 36)
    - National collection of chapter dues, 2001 (Box 52, Folder 37)
    - Grants to chapters, 2002 (Box 52, Folder 38)
    - Audit, 2002 (Box 52, Folder 39)
    - Financials, 2002-2003 (Box 52, Folder 40)
    - Expense Reports, 2003 (Box 52, Folder 41)
    - Retirement (Box 52, Folder 42)
    - Acknowledgments of contributions [ RESTRICTED], 1999 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Goodman, Paulette: Bio., Program for Fundraiser, 1988, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Graphic Artists: Todd Kendall, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Invitations: Regent Hospital, New York City, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Memberships, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Access: Networking in the Public Interest; Gay/Lesbian Parents Coalition International
  - Memberships, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Independent Charities of America
  - Memberships, 1988-1992 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Independent Sector, Inc.
  - Memberships, 1991-1993 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    National Association for the Exchange of Industrial Resources, National Self-Help Clearinghouse, National Society of Fund-Raising Executives
  - Needs Assessment Survey for Groups and Contacts, 3/1989 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Nominating Committee Notes and reports, 1987-1992 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Office Supplies, 1989-1993 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Miller's Office Products, Paul B. Williams Incorporated, Pennywise, Pitney-Bowes, RMRS Systems, Reliable
  - Office Supplies, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Staples orders and invoices
  - Office Supplies, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Stationery orders, invoices
  - Office Supplies, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    T. Talbott Bond Co., Catterton Printing, Commonwealth, Zzyzyx, Prestige Boxes, R. S. Willard Co., Inc., Diamond Container Corp., Xerox, Washington Council of Agencies
  - Open House invitations, mailing lists, sign-up sheets, art samples, art list, m/w: P-FLAG tattoo, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Orders: Vancouver chapter, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Permissions: Parenting for Peace and Justice Network, Karen W. Bauer, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Personnel: Employee Handbook, 2 editions, 1990, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Personnel: Employment Eligibility Verification form, staff list, employee performance evaluation form, personnel policies, meeting notes, Washington Council of Agencies Health Plan, 1991-1994 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - P-FLAG Federation Support of Research Projects procedures sheet, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Phones, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    AT and T, Bell Atlanticom Systems, Inc., Allnet, American Longlines, C and P Telephone, Target Distributing Co.
  - Position Description: Family Partners, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Printers, 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    Arcadia Press; CAI Printing; Centers for the Handicapped, Inc.; Ed. Spivey, Jr. Publication Design; EU Services; Frank Gumpert Printing Co., Inc.; Isis Group; Lucas Bros.; Malchow; Omnibus Press
  - Regional Directors
    - A-Sc: reports, questionnaires, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Sm-Z: reports, questionnaires, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Regional Director's Handbook, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 26-27)
    - Information and procedure for approving new prospects, general information, forms, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Meeting agendae, notes, reports, forms, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Meeting minutes and reports, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Regional Directors List, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Regional Directors' Council, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Regional Directors/Affiliates Desk Reference, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 13)
      copy belonging to Sidney Oliver
    - Regional Directors' Handbook, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Regional Director's handbook materials, 1991-1993 (Box 26, Folder 53)
    - Regional Director's meeting, Seattle, 9/1992 (Box 26, Folder 54)
    - Regional Director's Handbook, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 55)
    - Regional Director survey, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 56)
    - Regional Director's meeting, 9/1993 (Box 26, Folder 57)
    - Regional Director's meeting, San Francisco, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 58)
    - Regional Directors' council meeting, 1994? (Box 26, Folder 59)
    - Regional Director lists, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 60)
    - Regional Director Updates, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 61)
    - Leadership roster, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 62)
    - Information re: correcting mailing lists, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 63)
    - Atwood, Benowitz, Binder materials, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 64)
    - Boland, Bruyn, Dotts, Genasci materials, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 65)
    - Irvin, Larson, Levine, Morse materials, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 66)
    - Myers, Nardacci, Steele, THoron, Tully materials, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 67)
    - Regional Directors Committee history, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Regional Director's handbook materialsminutes, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Regional Director job description, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - RDs communications/resources, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - Central RD correspondence, 1996-1999 (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - Southern RD correspondence, 1996-1999 (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - Great Lakes RD correspondence, 1996-1999 (Box 41, Folder 28)
    - Heartlands RD correspondence, 1996-1999 (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - Heartlands RD correspondence: Carolyn Griffen, 1996-1999 (Box 41, Folder 30)
    - Northern Plains RD correspondence, 1996-1999 (Box 41, Folder 31)
    - Poconos RD correspondence, 1996-1999 (Box 41, Folder 32)
    - RD Council correspondence, 1996-1999 (Box 41, Folder 33)
    - RD Council/Board of Directors meeting, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 34)
    - RD policy, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 35)
    - RD workplans, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 36)
    - Regional Directors Resource Manual, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 37)
    - Regional Directors Resource Manual, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 38)
    - Regional Directors' meetings, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 43)
    - Regional Directors' Council, 1994 (Box 52, Folder 44)
    - South Atlantic Region, 1995-1997 (Box 52, Folder 45)
    - Regional Directorship materials, 1996-2001 (Box 52, Folder 46)
    - Regional Director Plans, 1997 (Box 52, Folder 47)
    - Nebraska, 1999-2000 (Box 52, Folder 48)
    - RD Council Meetings (Wash., D.C.), 2000 (Box 52, Folder 49)
    - Great Lakes: Michigan--Delphi Case, 2000 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Southern Region: Louisiana, 2000 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Heartlands Region: AR, 2000-2001 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Paths to Inclusivity, 2000-2001 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Central Region: WI, 2000-2002 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Regional Director Handbook, 2000-2002 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Southern Region: Texas, 2000-2002 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Northern Plains Region--RD, 2000-2003 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Minnesota, 2000-2003 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Central Region: RD, 2000-2003 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Great Lakes: Michigan, 2000-2003 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Great Lakes: Ohio, 2000-2002 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - RD Council Meeting (Denver), 2001 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - RD Nominees, 2001-2003 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Springfield, IL, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Heartlands Region: Missouri, 2002 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - RD Council Meeting (Columbus, OH), 2002 (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - RD Meetings, 2002-2003 (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - Heartland Region: KS, 2002-2003 (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - Chicago, 2002-2003 (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - Central Region: IA, 2002-2003 (Box 53, Folder 21)
    - RD Council Meeting, 2003 (Box 53, Folder 22)
    - Fort Wayne, 2003 (Box 53, Folder 23)
    - RD Meeting, May 2003 (Box 53, Folder 24)
    - RD Council Meetings (Washington, D.C.), 2003 (Box 53, Folder 25)
    - RD Meeting, July 2003 (Box 53, Folder 26)
    - Great Lakes: Indiana, 2003 (Box 53, Folder 27)
    - Central Region: IL, 2003 (Box 53, Folder 28)
    - Detroit Area, 2003 (Box 53, Folder 29)
    - Kalamazoo, 2003 (Box 53, Folder 30)
    - Indianapolis, 2003 (Box 53, Folder 31)
    - Heartland--Regional Director (Joyce Rock), 2003 (Box 53, Folder 32)
    - Great Lakes: Regional Director, Ann Wilger [ RESTRICTED], 1997-2003 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Research Screening Committee correspondence, notes, information sheets, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Reservations for Charles Sumner School: information, applications, rules, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Security, 1991-1993 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    Fire evacuation procedures, security guidelines, Kastle Security Systems information and correspondence
  - Self-Help directory listing information, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Shipping: UPS, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Northeast Regional Director Correspondence and Workplans, 2000-2006 (Box 67, Folder 21)
  - State Councils
    - State Councils, 1998 (Box 53, Folder 33)
    - Alaska Chapters and State Council, 1998-2001 (Box 53, Folder 34)
    - Oregon Chapters and State Council, 2000 (Box 53, Folder 35)
    - State Council Affiliation Agreement, 2000 (Box 53, Folder 36)
    - Iowa State Council, 2004 (Box 53, Folder 37)
    - State conferences: OR, FL, 2001, 2006 (Box 63, Folder 27-28)
  - Strategic Plan
    - Background, reports, 1988-1992 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Structure Committee notes, comments, correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Materials for Board meeting, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Strategic Planning Board retreat materials, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Goals Worksheets, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Executive Director's report to the P-FLAG Board of Directors, Agenda, committee and task force assignments, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Ray's worksheets, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Dan's worksheets, typing guidelines, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Lou's worksheets, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Dan Ray notes, group worksheet revisions, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Worksheet revisions and notes, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Staff retreat: instructions and worksheets, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Mission Statement, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Strategic Plans, 1990-1992 (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Strategic Plan, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 28-29)
    - Strategic Plan- completed items, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Strategic Plan Assignments, 8/1992 (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - Revision notes, 8/1992 (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - Strategic Plan boards, 4/1993 (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Report to Board, 8/1992 (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Meeting of the Strategic Plan committee 1, 10/24/1992 (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - Strategic Plan board structure evolution, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 36)
    - Strategy, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 37)
    - Strategic Working Actions Team (SWAT team), 1994 (Box 27, Folder 38)
    - SWAT team miscellaneous, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 39)
    - Strategic Plan, 1992 (Box 53, Folder 38)
    - ENDS, Budget, 1996-1997 (Box 53, Folder 39)
    - FY 99 Workplan--Field, Program, and Policy Department, 1998 (Box 53, Folder 40)
    - Board of Directors ENDS Committee, 1998 (Box 53, Folder 41)
    - ENDS, 1998 (Box 53, Folder 42)
    - ENDS, 1998-1999 (Box 53, Folder 43)
    - 1999-2000 Workplan and Budget, 1999 (Box 53, Folder 44)
    - Planning for Strategic Plan, 1999-2000 (Box 53, Folder 45)
    - Monitoring Reports, Sept. 1999, Dec. 1999, Jan. 2000, Apr. 2000 (Box 53, Folder 46)
    - ENDS Monitoring, 1999-2001 (Box 53, Folder 47)
    - Strategic Planning, 2000 (Box 53, Folder 48)
    - Strategic Planning Session, July 2000 (Box 53, Folder 49)
    - ENDS Committee Survey, ca.2000 (Box 53, Folder 50)
    - 2000-2001 Workplan, 2000-2001 (Box 53, Folder 51)
    - Strategic Planning, 2000-2003 (Box 53, Folder 52)
    - 2001-2002 Workplan, 2001-2002 (Box 53, Folder 53)
    - Field and Policy Strategic Planning, 2001-2004 (Box 53, Folder 54)
    - 2002-2003 Workplan Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 53, Folder 55)
    - Strategic Planning: Tulsa, Portland workshops, 1998-2000 (Box 63, Folder 25-26)
  - Affiliation: Information and forms, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Business Files: Forms and orders, 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Contacts: Names, addresses, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Directories
    - Files copy, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Board "Mini" directory, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - International list of chapters and contacts, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Self-help and referral, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Affiliated chapters and personal contacts, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Affiliate directory changes, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - General affiliate/board directories, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 37-38)
    - General affiliate/board directories, 1991-1992 (Box 24, Folder 39)
    - International chapter directories, 1991-19928 (Box 24, Folder 40)
    - Affiliate PO box list, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Contact board list, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Directory change problem file, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Entered chapter name lists, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Field affiliate labels, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Administrative directory: chapters, groups, and contacts, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Master chapter directory, 8/14/93 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Reality check: directory to-do list, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Spanish speakers directory, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - General chapter/contact directory, 6/1994 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Misc. directories, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 11)